I smell popcorn.
It's a little big.
But it's really calm.
I'm so excited.
Today is the day of the girl's
counterattack.
I'm so excited.
I'm a girl.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'm not going to be exposed like this.
I'm watching.
April 20th.
Cut.
I'm talking to myself.
I can't cut it because I'm talking to
myself.
I'm talking to myself.
Hello!
It's like a ghost!
2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
Rock on! We are TAKISEN!
Nice to meet you!
Thank you!
Thank you for giving birth to me.
You're so big!
I want to take a picture with you.
Thank you!
I'm wearing a ribbon because I admire
TAKISEN.
I thought there was no one in white.
I'm wearing a ribbon.
Thank you!
Rock on to your heart!
We are TAKIMEKI TEMPU!
Thank you!
It's our first time to have an event
like this on our 20th anniversary.
It's a project that fits the song,
which is cute at its best.
We want to make a positive and positive
future
for many people who have been sad about
their disappearance.
We want to do our best to make a bright
future for them.
I think it's rare to have an event like
this.
We are looking forward to it.
There are people who wrote their sad
stories.
I hope you can write your sad stories
with a smile.
Thank you!
I want to hold an event in a venue or a
place.
We have decided a new goal.
We want to hold an event in a venue or a
place.
Do you think you can do it?
I think I can do it.
I'm doing my best every day.
I'm having a lot of fun.
That is why I spent a time to shoot
seriously
By the way, I wore a green bag, so I
wore a blue bag for Hiori.
The staff was holding it from behind.
The staff was moving according to my
movement.
It was the highlight of the day.
It's a green bag.
It's going to disappear.
It's going to be a comedy.
But it was well reflected.
I hope that more and more people in the
world will know us.
I was wearing a green bag today.
I was wearing a green bag all the time.
I want to be a group that can challenge
new things.
Thank you for your hard work.
I have to say that I'm a little nervous.
I'm sorry for everyone.
Ta-da!
This is the new costume.
It's a earring.
And this is the new costume.
This is a bracelet.
It's cute.
We can't see this in the video.
We ate chocolate croissant together.
It was so delicious.
Canelé was also delicious.
This is it.
When we finish eating that, we can see
the chocolate croissant.
I'll eat a little.
How many do you have left?
Two.
You haven't eaten yet?
I haven't.
I'm going to have a press conference.
How many times have you done it
recently?
Yes, I have a press conference.
It's a cover song.
I'm getting used to it.
I'm happy to see that I'm shaking
properly.
Wow!
So cute!
I'm happy!
How do you live?
It's a wonderful life.
I can't do anything here.
It looks painful.
How do you do your hair?
I just do it.
You're very cooperative.
Today is April 20th, the day of the
maiden's departure.
The destination is the maiden's return.
The maiden's return.
We're going to listen to the episodes of
people who were disappointed and comfort
each other.
We'll listen to the episodes of many
people who were disappointed and try to
move everyone's heart forward.
Today, 2SX, the founder of singalong,
and a member of serial singer Sakifumi
have come to Policy Radio Underground.
And, B keinen Sx4 & Thr7n Ouchou Ni Jya-
oi
was singing live together.
We also perform live with the 2SX!
Also B ken Shoujo Tai held a live
performance recently.
I didn't know that.
The staff of the company told me to go
to take a picture.
So I went there.
I was surprised.
I thought they would take a picture
behind me.
But the staff of BASHOI told me to go
up.
So I went there.
I see.
BASHOI's fans were so kind.
They were so happy.
Some fans brought me a fine audio.
Really?
I was so happy.
They said, 「Kanami!」
I was happy that they knew our
existence.
Thank you.
I want to collaborate with BASHOI
someday.
We did it before.
We did it a long time ago.
I want to do it.
I'll go to practice.
I'll go.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
It's colorful.
Great.
It's amazing.
Everyone in the advertising club.
I'm scared.
Time...
Thank you.
She's coming from the audience.
I'm a little frustrated.
Rock on to your heart.
We are Super Exciting Send-off.
Thank you.
Today is the day of the love affair, so
we are going to have a girl's revenge
event.
Let's do it!
It's an event to make the past love
affairs come true.
We are going to dance the cutest thing
in the world and make the next love
affair.
We got the information from the
publicity staffs.
We are going to learn the love affairs
from them.
Let's start the first love affair.
I'm so excited.
Let's start.
I'm going to read it.
When I was in the second year of high
school, my boyfriend who I dated for a
year suddenly dumped me.
We were in the same kendo club, so we
had to see each other every day after
school.
I was full of regrets, so it was very
painful, but I thought that club
activities should not be broken up in
the club activities.
I was in a relationship with him every
day and we were in a love affair.
I don't know if he noticed it, but I
think it was a page of his mind.
You did your best!
Let's give them a big hand!
But I'm glad that we can't divide our
club into two.
That's great.
I'm a bit nervous.
I'm sure we'll meet better people in the
future.
You're going to be strong, right?
I'm going to want to fight!
I remember a lot.
We're going to dance to purify the
highest level of cuteness.
We're going to learn from each other.
I'm happy.
Let's go.
I think you can dance because the song
is playing.
Let's dance together.
Shall we go?
Let's learn together!
Let's go!
Caution ★AIーKEKKA!!!
I did it!
Did you do it?
Did you get purified?
I did it!
When I was eating dinner at a nice place
in Tokyo,
I thought I could do it,
but I confessed on the spot,
and I was completely...
Gyokusai?
Gyokusai!
It's okay!
It's cute!
I was completely Gyokusui!
Gyokusai!
Gyokusui!
No!
I'm sorry!
I was completely Gyokusai!
I turned the inside of my car into a
hellish atmosphere!
Now, I can laugh about it,
but I was shocked at my bad timing and
my broken heart.
It's quite far from Tokyo to Nagoya, so
it's a long time.
It's 4 or 5 hours.
I think it'll take 4 or 5 hours.
It was a shocking episode,
but I think you were able to give up
because you're the best.
Let's move on to the positive part.
Let's sing and dance together,
and move on to the positive part.
Everyone.
Thank you, I'm the best!
I suddenly became cute!
Let me dance!
I somehow became cute!
You utilized for me, I'm the most
evolving cute girl
This is a world's fastest $h!tting music
video.
I'm short of eyes.
I mean,
I'm so full of cuteness.
we did a lot of shooting in many places.
Like that white,
bright castle.
The wedding venue.
Oh, the wedding venue.
And also, a CG pop
world view.
We did it in Green Park.
The single is released on May 29th.
There are many events after this.
Yes, there are.
So, please check it on our website.
Of course, you can check it on our
website.
But, please check it again.
Well,
it's time to say good bye.
Bye.
It's time to say good bye.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Please give a big applause
to all the staffs.
Thank you.
Please give a big applause to the
staffs.
Thank you.
Great!
Everyone did a great job!
Thank you for your hard work!
It was our first time trying this kind
of event.
We've never heard of this kind of event
before.
So we were wondering how it would be.
After hearing everyone's sad story,
we were a little sad, too.
But we danced together and shared our
feelings.
We were supposed to start the song,
right?
We danced together!
We danced well.
It was a good event.
We danced to the song that everyone was
sad about.
Oh, that's good!
We were sad that we couldn't dance.
Let's do the reverse dance!
Let's do it!
Don't do that!
Oh!
Finally!
We're finally doing it.
Oh, right!
The new album!
It's so cute.
It's the first time we're releasing a
new album.
It's so cute.
Yeah, it is.
It's like we've never done it before.
I love it.
When we dance.
Yeah.
I think you'll be able to see us as
fresh as we are.
So, everyone, please get ready to speak
out loud and move your body.
Please come see us!
We'll be waiting for you!
Please subscribe to the channel!
I can say it now, I'm not lost on why
I'm crying
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the
rainbow is ringing
I'm playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye
Goodbye to me from yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a flower
I'll dry my tears
And wear a rainbow dress
Thank you for watching!